Guide to the Mann Library. Division of Collection Development records, 1979-2006.
Mann Library. Division of Collection Development records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Mann Library. Division of Collection Development records, 1979-2006.
13-18-3618
Albert R. Mann Library.Division of Collection Development.
2 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Contents include: Activities of the Faculty, committee reports, correspondence, Full Text Project reports, CALS 75th Anniversary information, user surveys, user statistics, including SWIG (Simplified Wrapped Interface Generator), reference stats, a doorbell system for reference patrons, and collection guidelines for academic departments in CALS.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Contents include: Activities of the Faculty, committee reports, correspondence, Full Text Project reports, CALS 75th Anniversary information, user surveys, user statistics, including SWIG (Simplified Wrapped Interface Generator), reference stats, a doorbell system for reference patrons, and collection guidelines for academic departments in CALS.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Albert R. Mann Library.
Subjects:
Library collection development--New York (State)--Ithaca.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
  - Activities of Faculty - NYS CALS, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on Plant Molecular Biology (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural History Symposium (Hosted by CU), September 9-11, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Antiquarian Bookman, 1962-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - End Use of Bibliographic Databases - Project Report, July 30, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Binding Information - Stiffening, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ornithology Library - Collection Procedure, February 28, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Collection Policy Progress Lists, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CUL Committees, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Computers and Searching for Bibliographic Information (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Conservation Technician - Job Description, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Core Literature of Agricultural Sciences - Reception, July 23, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Dr. Toge Johansson, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Data Analysis - Use of Computerized Literature Search Services, June 27, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Data Documentation - Survey of Dialog Users, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Full-Text Working Group, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Full-Text Working Group, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Full-Text Working Group, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bas-Frieze - Abbe Sculpture - Correspondence, Photographs, 1953-1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Mann Library - Staff Handbook, 1958-1965 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - CALS 75th Anniversary Guide, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - SWIG - Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Agricultural and Biological Engineering, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Animal Science, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Biochemistry, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Biometrics, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Communications, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Consumer Economics and Housing, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Design and Environmental Analysis (DEA), 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Ecology, Evolution, and Systematics, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Education, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Entomology, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Food Science, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Genetics and Development, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Horticulture, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Hotel Administration, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Human Development and Family Studies, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Human Service Studies (HSS), 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Microbiology, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Natural Resources, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Neurobiology and Behavior, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Nutritional Science, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Physiology, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Plant Biology, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Plant Breeding, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Plant Pathology, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Rural Sociology, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Soil, Crop, and Atmospheric Sciences, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Textiles and Apparel, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Database Statistics - Reference, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Mann Gateway, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Natural History Microfilming Project - Procedures, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Reference Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Reference Notes, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Reference Notes, 1992, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Reference Notes, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Reference Notes, 1997-2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Reference Notes, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Reference Statistics - Email, July 10, 2006-October 1, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Reference Statistics - Saturday-Sunday, Fall 2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Reference Desk "Door Chime" - Patron Call Button (Box 2)